Park Place, The Gallery of Art Research, Inc. and Paula Cooper Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Paula Cooper Gallery, 1962-2006, Series 3:; (Boxes 4-49, 51; 45.7 linear feet)
  - Business Files, 1968-1996, bulk 1980s-1990s, 3.2:
    - Advertising (Box 13)
      - Exhibition Announcement Cards and Cost Comparisons, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Finished Ads (July 1992 - ), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Graphics/Layouts, 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Listings, 1987-1993, (4 folders) (Box 13, Folder 22-25)
    - Advertising (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous, 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Prints of Unidentified Artwork, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Rate Cards, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Schedule and Contracts, 1990-1993, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
    - Entre Computer Center, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Events (Box 14)
      - Announcements and Miscellaneous, circa 1969-1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Chamber Music, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Deborah Hay Performance (Feb. 1979), 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Gertrude Stein Reading, 1975-1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Peace Festival Poster, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Inventory Notebook, circa 1968 - early 1970s (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Opening of New Gallery, 1968, circa 1973 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Renovations (Box 14)
      - 149 Wooster St., 1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - 149 Wooster St. Architectural Plans, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - 149 Wooster St. Building Notice Application, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - 149-153 Wooster St. Construction, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - 149-155 Wooster St. (1985), 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - 155 Wooster St. Basement Renovation (1990), 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - 155 Wooster St. Doors to Replace Windows (1986), 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - 155 Wooster St. First Floor, Harken Plumbing Heating Proposal, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - 155 Wooster St. Fourth Floor Floor Plan, Max Gordon, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - 155 Wooster St. Fourth Floor Renovations (Aug. 31, 1988 - Sept. 1, 1989), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - 155 Wooster St. Revised Drawing, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Air Conditioning, Nelson Air Devices (July 1982), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Air Conditioning Repair, Master Cooling Corp. Contract (Apr. 1984), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Architectural Drawings, circa mid-1980s (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Basement Asbestos Spraying (1984), 1979, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Basement Construction (Summer 1979), 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Bathroom Renovation (Summer 1978), 1978 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Certificate of Capital Improvement, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Environmental Control Board, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Fire Exit, NYC Approval, 1984, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Floor Renovation (Dec. 1989), 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - Fourth Floor Renovation, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Front Door, Landmark Preservation Commission Approval, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - Front Wall and Alarm Area (July 12, 1978), 1978 (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - Gallery (1973, 1980), 1973-1974, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - Gallery (1974), 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 40)
      - Gallery (1981), Una Architectural Studios, Townsend and Carmello, 1981, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 41)
      - Gallery Doors (May 8, 1987), 1987 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Renovations (Box 15)
      - Gallery Renovations (1992), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Gallery Renovation (1993), 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Gallery Renovation/Improvement (1973-1979), 1972-1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Gallery Renovation Paid Bills (Sept. 1, 1983 - Aug. 31, 1986), 1983-1986, (3 folders) (Box 15, Folder 4-6)
      - Gallery Renovation, Tri-Cross Contracting, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Heat Consultant, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Peter Dechar, Inc. Storage Built-In Cabinet, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Plans for Fire Door and Sliding Door, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Re-Lining Gallery Walls (Summer 1989), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Renovation Costs, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Skylights, 1981, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Third Floor, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Artists' Files, 1962-2006, bulk mid-1970s-early 2000s, 3.3:
    This series contains materials gathered by the gallery about the artists in its stable; considerable documentation is found for Jennifer Bartlett, Peter Campus, Zoe Leonard, Elizabeth Murray, Alan Shields, and the estate of Tony Smith. Materials are varied and may include correspondence with artists, museums, and galleries regarding installations, artwork fabrication, and other business; biographies and bibliographies; exhibition files; printed materials; and photographic materials of artwork and installations. The folders are arranged alphabetically by artist's last name; thereafter folders are arranged according to the order of the material upon accession. Photographic materials are generally found at the end of the artists' materials and are arranged in rough chronological order by artwork date.
    - Artschwager, Richard, 1966-1973 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Barr, Burt (Box 15)
      - Videography and Installation Instructions, circa 1996 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Complete Bibliography, circa 1994 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Videography and Biographical Sketch, circa 1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Press Release, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Video Synopses, circa 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Reviews, 1986-1994 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - The Israel Museum, Jerusalem, 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - "The Pool," Deutsche Bank, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - "The Pool," Musee D'Art Contemporain de Montreal, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Mailing List, circa 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer (Box 15)
      - Walker Art Center, Minneapolis, MN, 1982-1985, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 27-28)
      - Cleopatra, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Cesar Pelli Commisssion at Washington National Airport, Arlington, VA, 1993-1997, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 30-31)
      - Homan-ji Temple, Chiba, Japan, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - New Amsterdam Beer, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - [Inquiries], Julie Graham, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - [Correspondence], 1985-1997, (4 folders) (Box 15, Folder 35-38)
      - "Jennifer Bartlett: Don't Talk!," Mathieu Carriere, Portmanteau Press, NY, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 39)
      - Agreements with Paula Cooper Gallery, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 40)
      - [ISI Drawing], 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 41)
      - Chase Manhattan Bank Offering, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 42)
      - 24 Hours Print Edition, 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer (Box 16)
      - In the Garden, Saatchi Collection, 1992-1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Fia, Inc., 1991-1993, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
      - 24 Hours Abrams Contract, 1991-1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Gallery Camino Real (Jan. 1-27, 1994), 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - San Francisco International Airport, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Glass of Water I and Glass of Water II Prints, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Shadow Prints, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Naoshima Museum, Japan, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Eidelson v. Bartlett, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Bartlett Book ["History of the Universe"], 1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - At Sands Point, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - La Jolla [Exhibition], 1985 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Brooklyn Museum, Brooklyn, NY, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Carnegie, circa 1980s (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Viart Corporation, The Capital Group Companies, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, Buffalo, NY, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - In the Garden, Margo Leavin Gallery, Los Angeles, CA, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Up the Creek/To the Island, circa 1982-1985 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - The Tate Gallery, London, England, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Notes for Walker and Volvo, circa 1980s (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - The Cleveland Museum of Art, Cleveland, OH, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Rhapsody Book, Harry N. Abrams, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Rhapsody, 1976-1986, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 24-25)
      - Rhapsody Photos and Instructions, circa 1979 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Announcements and Information, 1973-1984 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Up the Creek/To the Island Descriptions [Disbound material], circa 1982 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Damage/Insurance, 1977-1984 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Books and Writings, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1985, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 31-32)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer (Box 17)
      - Larson Framing, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - 9th Biennale de Paris, 1975, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Exhibition Lists, 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - In the Garden Drawings, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Carleton College, Northfield, MN, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - In the Garden Book Party, Harry N. Abrams, Inc., 1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - History of the Universe, 1985, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Poem, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Book, Harry N. Abrams, Inc., Elmore Leonard, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Long Beach Museum of Art, Long Beach, CA, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Walker Art Center Loan Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Walker Art Center, Minneapolis, MN, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Milwaukee Art Museum, Milwaukee, WI, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Sonoma State University Prints Exhibition, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Atlanta Commission, 1977-1981 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Volvo Commission, 1983-1984, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Denver Commission, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Saatchi Commission, circa 1980s (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Bartlett Expenses, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Homan-ji Temple, Chiba, Japan, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous, circa early 1990s (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Photograph and Slides, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Seibu Commission, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Station Fine Arts Program, Baltimore, MD, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - AT&T Commission, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - ISI, Philadelphia, PA, 1978-1983, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 26-27)
      - Seibu Commission, Four Seasons, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Rambert Dance Company Projects, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Opera Comique, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Prints, 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Battery Park Garden, 1986-1991 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Swid Powell Design Contract, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Simca Print Artists, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Rhapsody Documentation, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - At Sea Japan Print (JBa-5-PRT), 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - Graceland Mansion Print (JBa-1-PRT), 1978-1984 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - American Dance Festival, 1978-1984 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - In the Garden No. 118, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 39)
      - In the Garden No. 190, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 40)
      - In the Garden No. 40, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - In the Garden No. 116, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - Elements - Air, Fire, Earth, Water Prints, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - Knoedler Gallery, London, England, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 44)
      - Play, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 45)
      - NYC Parks Department Poster, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 46)
      - Kurata Interview Pending, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 47)
      - Lincoln Center Film Society Poster, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 48)
      - Lincoln Center Chamber Music Festival Poster, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 49)
      - Shipping, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 50)
      - House With Open Door Shipping, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer (Box 18)
      - Book, la difference, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Decca CD Cover, Composer Aaron Kernis, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - The Comedian as the Letter C, Citibank, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Rizzoli Childrens Book, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Orlando Museum of Art Print Retrospective, Orlando, FL, 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Kotobuki Seating Co., Japan, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Maier Museum of Art, Randolph-Macon Women's College, Lynchburg, VA, 1977, 1990- 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Art Tower Mito, Japan, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Pending, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Simca Print Artists, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Available Works List with Valuations, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Pending, Heath Gallery, Atlanta, GA, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Inventory Notes [Also Includes Inventory Notes for Andre, Serrano and Shields], 1990- 1995 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Returns, 1994-1998 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - [Exhibitions, Miscellaneous], 1980s-1995, (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
      - At Sands Point Paintings, Exhibition Format, circa 1986 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Homan-ji, Greg Kucera Gallery, Seattle, WA, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Homan-ji, Gallery Camino Real, Boca Raton, FL, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Hiram Butler Commission, St. Stephen's Episcopal Church, Houston, TX, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Homan-ji, Andre Emmerich Gallery, New York, NY, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Numark Gallery, Washington, DC, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions Outside the Gallery, circa 1996 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Seibu, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Bard College, Annandale-on-Hudson, NY, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Detroit Institute of Arts Exhibition (June 10 - Sept. 13, 1987), Detroit, MI, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Exhibition (Feb. 21 - Mar. 21, 1987), circa 1987 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - Fia, Inc., 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Up the Creek and To the Island Condition Report, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, Photographs (Box 18)
      - Portraits of the Artist, circa 1979-1995 (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Artwork (1969), circa 1988 (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - Prints, circa 1980s (Box 18, Folder 32)
      - Artwork (1970-1971), circa 1970-1990s (Box 18, Folder 33)
      - Artwork (1972), circa 1972-1988 (Box 18, Folder 34)
      - Artwork (1973), circa 1973-1980s (Box 18, Folder 35)
      - Artwork (1974), circa 1974-1988 (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - Artwork (1975-1976), circa 1975-1990s (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - Rhapsody (1975-1976), circa 1975-1990s (Box 18, Folder 38)
      - Artwork (1977), circa 1977-1990s (Box 18, Folder 39)
      - Installations (1977), circa 1977-1990s (Box 18, Folder 40)
      - Graceland Mansion (1978-1979), circa 1978-1990s (Box 18, Folder 41)
      - Artwork (1978), circa 1978-1990s (Box 18, Folder 42)
      - Artwork (1979), circa 1979-1990s (Box 18, Folder 43)
      - Swimmers Atlanta (1979), circa 1979-1990s (Box 18, Folder 44)
      - In the Garden (1980), circa 1980-1990s (Box 18, Folder 45)
      - In the Garden Drawings (1980), circa 1980-1990s (Box 18, Folder 46)
      - Artwork (1980), circa 1980-1990s (Box 18, Folder 47)
      - Installation (Jan. 9 - Feb. 7, 1981), circa 1981-1990s (Box 18, Folder 48)
      - In the Garden (1981), circa 1981-1990s (Box 18, Folder 49)
      - Up the Creek (1981-1982), circa 1981-1990s (Box 18, Folder 50)
      - In the Garden (1982), circa 1982-1990s (Box 18, Folder 51)
      - To the Island (1982), circa 1982-1990s (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, Photographs (Box 19)
      - Artwork (1983), circa 1983-1990s (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Artwork and Installations (1984), circa 1984-1990s (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Blue House, Unfinished (1985), 1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Volvo Corporate Headquarters, circa 1980s (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - AT&T Commission (1984), circa 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Installations (1984-1985), circa 1984-1990s (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Installation (Apr. 4-27, 1985), circa 1985-1990s (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Luxembourg Garden Carnegie Institute Installation, circa 1985-1990s (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - At Sands Point, Nos. 1-52 (1985-1986), circa 1986-1990s, (5 folders) (Box 19, Folder 9-13)
      - Old House Lane, Nos. 1-34 (1986-1987), circa 1986-1990s, (3 folders) (Box 19, Folder 14-16)
      - Four Paintings for Victor Ganz (1987), 1987-1990s (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Artwork (1988), circa 1988-1990s (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Fire Series (1988-1989), circa 1989-1990s (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Fire Series, London (1988-1989), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Not Fire Series Paintings (1989), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Black and White Drawings and Prints (1990), circa 1989-1990s (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Artwork (1990), circa 1989-1990s (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Artwork (1991), 1990s (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Installation 3 Views (Jan. 5 - Feb. 2, 1991), circa 1991 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - The Four Seasons (1990-1992), 1990s (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Air: 24 Hours Series, JBA#735-758 (1991-1992), 1992-1993, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 27-28)
      - Artwork (1992), circa 1992-1997 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Commission for Homan-ji Temple, Chiba, Japan (May 1992), 1992 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Air: 24 Hours Series (1993), 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Alphabet Series (1993), 1993 (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - Alphabet Installation (Jan. 7-29, 1994), 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - Artwork (1994), circa 1994 (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - Earth Series (1995), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, Transparencies (Box 19)
      - Artwork (1977), circa 1977-1990s (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - Artwork (1978), circa 1978-1990s (Box 19, Folder 37)
      - Artwork (1978-1979), circa 1978-1990s (Box 19, Folder 38)
      - Artwork (1979), circa 1979-1990s (Box 19, Folder 39)
      - Artwork (1979-1980), circa 1979-1990s (Box 19, Folder 40)
      - Artwork (1980), circa 1980-1990s, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 41-42)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, Transparencies (Box 20)
      - In the Garden Installation (1981), circa 1981-1990s, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
      - Up the Creek and To the Island Installation (1981-1982), circa 1981-1990s (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Up the Creek (1981-1982), circa 1981-1990s (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - To the Island (1981-1982), circa 1981-1990s (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - In the Garden (1981-1982), circa 1981-1990s, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 6-7)
      - Artwork (1983-1984), circa 1983-1990s, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 8-9)
      - The Creek Series Dupes (1984), circa 1984-1990s (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - AT&T Commission (1984), circa 1984-1990s (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Prints (1984), circa 1984-1990s (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - The Island Series (1984-1985), circa 1984-1990s (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Prints (1985), circa 1985-1990s (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Sea Wall (1985), circa 1985-1990s (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - At Sands Point (1985-1986), circa 1985-1990s, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
      - Artwork (1987), circa 1987-1990s (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Four Paintings for Victor Ganz Dupes (1987), circa 1987-1990s (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Old House Lane (1986-1987), circa 1986-1990s, (3 folders) (Box 20, Folder 20-22)
      - House With Open Door (1988), circa 1988-1990s (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, Transparencies (Box 21)
      - Artwork (1988), circa 1988-1990s (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Fire Series (1988-1989), circa 1988-1990s (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Artwork (1989), circa 1988-1990s (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Not Fire Series (1989), circa 1989-1990s (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Installations (1989), circa 1989-1990s (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Paintings (1990), circa 1990-1997 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Drawings and Prints (1990), circa 1990-1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Fire Paintings Installation (Jan. 1990), circa 1990-1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Artwork (1991), circa 1990-1997 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Paintings (1991), circa 1991-1997 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Air: 24 Hours Series (1991-1992), circa 1991-1997, (4 folders) (Box 21, Folder 11-14)
      - Commission for Homan-ji Temple (1992), circa 1992-1997, (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
      - Alphabet Series (1993), circa 1993-1997 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Paintings (1993), circa 1993-1997 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, Transparencies (Box 22)
      - Prints (1992-1993), circa 1992-1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Air: 24 Hours Pastels Series (1993), circa 1993-1997, (2 folders) (Box 22, Folder 2-3)
      - Paintings (1994), circa 1994-1997 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Transparencies, Earth Series (1995), circa 1995-1997, (2 folders) (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer (Box 22)
      - Slides, Homan-ji III, circa 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Photographic Materials, Available Artwork, circa 1980s-1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Photographs, Available Plate Pieces, 1972-1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Photocopies of Photographic Materials, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Photograph Book of Commissions [Disassembled], circa 1980s-1990s, (2 folders) (Box 22, Folder 11-12)
      - Negatives, Design Portfolio, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Negatives and Contact Prints, circa 1972-1990s (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous Color Snapshots and Polaroids of Artwork, 1970s-1990s, (4 folders) (Box 22, Folder 15-18)
    - Bennett, Charles, Slides, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Berlant, Tony, circa 1978 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Birnbaum, Dara (Box 23)
      - Exhibition Announcements - Other Galleries, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - "Hostage" Video, 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 23, Folder 4-5)
      - Kunsthalle Wien, Vienna, Austria, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Rio Videowall, Rio Shopping/Entertainment Complex, Atlanta, GA, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Exhibition Information, circa 1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Progressive Insurance Company, Cleveland, OH, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Press (1980-1993) [Photocopies], circa 1980s-1990s, (10 folders) (Box 23, Folder 10-19)
      - Complete Biography, circa 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Bibliography, circa 1993 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Biography, circa 1992 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - "Hostage" Statement, circa 1994 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - [Correspondence], 1992-1994 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Biography (dbcom.bio), circa 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - dbcom.bib and dbvid.bio [empty folders], circa 1990s (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Four Gates Proposal, circa 1994 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Notes and Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Installations, circa 1992 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Background Information, circa 1994 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Press (1980-1989), 1980s-1990s (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Press (1991-1994), 1990s (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Press, Foreign (1982-1988), 1980s (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Camnitzer, Luis, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Campus, Peter, [Correspondence], 1989-2002 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Campus, Peter (Box 24)
      - [Correspondence], 1989-2002 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Works Dispute, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - A Spider Waits, ICA Philadelphia, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Printed Material, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Middlebury College Museum of Art Exhibition (Mar. - May 3, 1998), 1997 (Box 24, Folder 5)